https://hpsjewelers.com/privacy-policy/

Unique
Special (Discount Applied)
Site Information
Loading... Please wait...
Sign in or Create an account
Cart:
Unique
Special (Discount Applied)
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, HPS Estate Jewelers (HPS) collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. HPS’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our website(s). From time to time, HPS may release non-personally-identifying information in part or in the aggregate (e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our websites).
HPS also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on article pages and/or on HPS’ blogs. HPS only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to HPS’ websites choose to interact with HPS in ways that require HPS to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that HPS gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we may ask visitors who sign up for a newsletter or mailing list profile at HPS to provide a username and email address. This information may be used to offer additional content, features, goods and/or services in the future (e.g. a user that completes a survey may be offered content or services based on the information provided in survey responses). Those who engage in transactions with HPS – by purchasing product for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, HPS collects such information as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with HPS, as well as to offer additional relevant products and services in the future. HPS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
HPS may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, HPS may monitor the most popular blogs in our Forums, or most read articles on HPS’ website. HPS may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, HPS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
HPS discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on HPS’ behalf or to provide services available at HPS’ websites, or (ii) offer relevant and valuable services that we believe may be of interest to our customers and website visitors, or (iii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using HPS’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Additionally HPS may disclose potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when HPS believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of HPS, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of any HPS website and have supplied your email address, HPS may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with HPS and our products. We also use our various websites and forums to communicate this type of information. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. HPS takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. HPS uses cookies to improve our visitors’ experiences, to help HPS identify and track visitors, their usage of HPS website, and their website access preferences. HPS visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using HPS’ websites, with the drawback that certain features of HPS’ websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If HPS, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that HPS goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of HPS may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Advertisements
Advertisements appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by HPS and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Posted Comments
Comments, user-feedback, testimonials and other content submitted to our forums or comments made on our blog will be deemed to be the property of HPS, and may be reproduced at HPS’ sole discretion.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, HPS may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in HPS’ sole discretion. HPS encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a HPS forum account, you should also check the forum homepage for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
View the new gems added to our treasure chest
Sign up Today for Treasures of the Week
Name
Email
Quick Links
About Us
eCommerce Terms of Use
Friends of Oasis Day Spa
Special (Discount Applied)
72 Bowery, New York, NY 10013
1-877-HPS-JEWELERS (477-5393)
